and then come up high rep so pump them
out
yep
squeeze perfect
going for 30 three
more now hold this for 10 seconds 10 9 8
7 push your hips up higher there 5 4 3 2
good go for
it
perfect go down a little
deeper that's it
perfect little deeper
yeah that's it
perfect
perfect how many couple more
you've got 15 let's get five more 16
four more
17 18 two more come up high 19 last one
hold it for 10 seconds 20 1 2 3 4 come
up higher 5 6 7 8 9 10
good you dead yes go for it no you think
you'll get like
yeah don't go down as
far good
not as far go right there
yep good okay
Angie good for
perfect okay DG you'll breing it like
five just come up as high as you can
[Applause]
nice keep
going good job there you got 15 ice okay
all right now take off a band Diana
you're
up probably
20 20 to
30 maybe you'll get
30 pump them out one 2 three deeper four
five deeper 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 squeeze the top 22 good
23 24 25 26 27 28 two more 29 30
good squeeze GL good four 5 6 7 eight
good
9 10 11 12
13 good job
Angie nice
two
more nice good siege
he was a lot harder than the first
yeah good
good job
C good
job nice okay
di let's go uh let's go one
band this you'll probably
get 50 50 rep burnout 50 yeah this will
be easy one band
might be done at 12 30 or
40 what are you at 30
Hold the top for 10 seconds one 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9 10
good you
okay okay 50 reps two three four
16 nice 20 more
good
[Music]
jobie nice good job Angie Hold the top
for 10 seconds on your last
one hold it squeeze
good 8 9 10 good good job
you good
Angie
okayed all right Siege do as many you
can I'm thinking 30 reps
nice good job C
10 seconds 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
good awesome good